[{                                          
    "questionId": 1,
    "question": "It is the property that describes various characteristics of an entity.",
    "options": {
        "A" : "Column",
        "B" : "Attribute",
        "C" : "ER Diagram",
        "D" : "Relationship"
    },
    "answer": "B"
},
{
    "questionId": 2,
    "question": "It is an association between entities.",
    "options": {
        "A" : "One to One",
        "B" : "Specialization",
        "C" : "Relation",
        "D" : "Generalization"
    },
    "answer": "C"
},
{
    "questionId": 3,
    "question": "______ stores metadata about the structure of the database.",
    "options": {
        "A" : "Query Analyzer",
        "B" : "Data Catalog",
        "C" : "Physical database",
        "D" : "Data Dictionary"
    },
    "answer": "D"
},
{
    "questionId": 4,
    "question": "It is the minimal super key.",
    "options": {
        "A" : "Candidate Key",
        "B" : "Unique Key",
        "C" : "Primary Key",
        "D" : "Alternate Key"
    },
    "answer": "A"
},
{
    "questionId": 5,
    "question": "Foreign Key can be Null.",
    "options": {
        "A" : "False",
        "B" : "True"
    },
    "answer": "B"
},
{
    "questionId": 6,
    "question": "All the primary keys should be super keys.",
    "options": {
        "A" : "True",
        "B" : "False"
    },
    "answer": "A"
},
{
    "questionId": 7,
    "question": "What is the function of a database?",
    "options": {
        "A" : "to check all spellings",
        "B" : "to output data",
        "C" : "to check all input data",
        "D" : "to collect and organize input data"
    },
    "answer": "D"
},
{
    "questionId": 8,
    "question": "What is the language that is used by most DBMSs for helping their users to access data?",
    "options": {
        "A" : "SQL",
        "B" : "4GL",
        "C" : "High level language",
        "D" : "Query language"
    },
    "answer": "D"
},
{
    "questionId": 9,
    "question": "Information can be transferred between the DBMS and ______.",
    "options": {
        "A" : "Graphics program",
        "B" : "Word processor program",
        "C" : "Spreadsheet program",
        "D" : "All of the above"
    },
    "answer": "D"
},
{
    "questionId": 10,
    "question": "______ can be used as a primary key for a student file.",
    "options": {
        "A" : "Social Security Number",
        "B" : "Major",
        "C" : "Class",
        "D" : "GPA"
    },
    "answer": "A"
},
{
    "questionId": 11,
    "question": "A record management system ______.",
    "options": {
        "A" : "can be used to extract information stored in a computer file",
        "B" : "always uses a list as its model",
        "C" : "can handle many files of information at a time",
        "D" : "both a and b"
    },
    "answer": "A"
},
{
    "questionId": 12,
    "question": "It is a command that lets user to change one or more fields in a record.",
    "options": {
        "A" : "modify",
        "B" : "lookup",
        "C" : "insert",
        "D" : "update"
    },
    "answer": "A"
},
{
    "questionId": 13,
    "question": "Database management systems are intended to ______.",
    "options": {
        "A" : "establish relationship among records in different files",
        "B" : "maintain data integrity",
        "C" : "eliminate data redundancy",
        "D" : "manage file access",
        "E" : "all of the above"
    },
    "answer": "E"
},
{
    "questionId": 14,
    "question": "The language used application programs to request data from the DBMS is referred to as the ______",
    "options": {
        "A" : "DML",
        "B" : "DDL",
        "C" : "query language",
        "D" : "none of the above"
    },
    "answer": "A"
},
{
    "questionId": 15,
    "question": "It is a collection of operations that performs single logical function in a database application.",
    "options": {
        "A" : "Concurrent operation",
        "B" : "Durability",
        "C" : "Transaction",
        "D" : "Atomicity"
    },
    "answer": "C"
},
{
    "questionId": 16,
    "question": "The problem that is compounded when constraints involve several data items from different files are called ______.",
    "options": {
        "A" : "Security Problem",
        "B" : "Durability Problem",
        "C" : "Transaction Control Management Problem",
        "D" : "Integrity Problem"
    },
    "answer": "D"
},
{
    "questionId": 17,
    "question": "Ensuring atomicity is the responsibility of the ______ component",
    "options": {
        "A" : "Buffer Manager",
        "B" : "Transaction Manager",
        "C" : "File Manager",
        "D" : "DBA"
    },
    "answer": "B"
},
{
    "questionId": 18,
    "question": "Using relational model we design conceptual database design.",
    "options": {
        "A" : "True",
        "B" : "False"
    },
    "answer": "B"
},
{
    "questionId": 19,
    "question": "Tables are required to have at least one column.",
    "options": {
        "A" : "True",
        "B" : "False"
    },
    "answer": "A"
},
{
    "questionId": 20,
    "question": "In Relational Database data is stored as record types and the relationship is represented by set types.",
    "options": {
        "A" : "True",
        "B" : "False"
    },
    "answer": "A"
}
]
